Taylor Olds

St. Augustine, FL

Summary

After 4 years of full time parenting and being a student I am eager to incorporate new opportunities into my life. With a strong background in Information technology systems and customer service, I am prepared with knowledge of troubleshooting and operations of hardware and software across different media including desktop computers, laptop computers, phones, and network switches. I am highly motivated, creative, hardworking, and ready to make a great addition to any team.

Skills

Microsoft Office Adobe indesign Adobe Photoshop T/S Clearance Multitasking Prioritizing

Active Directory
Service desk
Comptia A+
Comptia Security +
Resource management
Troubleshooting

Remedy
Teamwork
Leadership
Event Planning
Attention to detail
Budgeting

Education

University of Maryland University College
General Studies Associate's Degree - June 2022
University of Maryland University College

BS Digital Media and Web technology & Marketing - June 2022-Present

Professional Experience

Full time Student & Parent

Multiple Locations May 2018-Present

- -Creating and balancing a family of four budget, paying bills, identifying cost saving opportunities, and eliminating extraneous spending.
- -Organized and collaborated to maintain family members' schedules , vacations , and a cross country move.
- -Social media networking to manage community gatherings and personal relationships.
- -Coordinated personal schedule with family and school while maintaining a 3.8 GPA in General Studies Associated Degree.

Professional Experience Continued

Information Systems Technician Navy

NCTSCU OKC Oklahoma City, Oklahoma March 2016-May 2018

Team Lead

- -Directed a team of 6 employees while ensuring 100 percent connectivity on 10 varying critical communication circuits.
- -System Administrator for Top secret message processing UNIX system. Created, maintained, and monitored usage of 25 user and administrator accounts.
- -Managed time critical troubleshooting of virtual machines discrepancies on 2 Dell servers during high paced military simulations.

Information Systsems Technician Navy

NCTS Bahrain Manama, Bahrain December 2013-December 2016

Field service Technician

- -Resolved over 300 trouble tickets using Remedy in support of 6,473 Outside Continental United States Navy enterprise Network users.
- -Launched a software migration of 20 pilot stations resulting in the 100% complete eradication of Windows XP for the area of responsibility.
- -Directed the repair of a faulty network switch, resulting in the restoration of critical network services to 25 user workstations.
- -Supervised a seamless relocation and installation of hardware including 14 user workstations and 2 network printers.

Medical Records Clerk

IOD Incorporated Multiple Locations, Florida May 2012-Mar 2013

- -Responsible for processing all release of information specifically medical record requests in a timely and efficient manner.
- Ensured accuracy of records and provided customers with the highest quality product and customer service.
- -Safeguarded customer medical records and release of records in compliance with HIPAA regulations and company policy.